# RARES BUCUR

## **CONTACT**

Address: Piata Victoriei nr. 4 (Relocation)

Phone: +40753307744

Email: rares.bucur99@yahoo.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/raresbucur

Website: https://raresbuc.github.io/RaresPortfolio/

## **SKILLS**

- Experienced in multiple technologies and programming languages such as Autodesk Maya, Substance Painter, ZBrush, Blender, Unreal Engine, Photoshop, Python, JavaScript, C++, Git, Agile development
- I am always thinking about how I can digitally reproduce what I see in the physical world and I also spend a lot of my free time observing how others reproduce physical phenomena, especially within the video game industry and interactive media.
- The ability to adapt to every type of person in a professional manner through communication in order to get the task at hand done
- Being up to date to anything new in the industry by interacting in various communities and following a lot of video game and film related groups and channels
- I consider myself a perfectionist when it comes to work on a project I love
- Great attention to details
- Language skills: English (Professional Proficiency), Romanian (Native),
  French (Elementary Proficiency)

I have worked on multiple projects within and outside of my Computer Science degree programme, such as different CGI projects with a strong aim on prop and environment art development. I am able to create high poly hard-surface models with great attention to details and topology and a very good understanding of game art workflows including UV unwrapping, shading, texturing, lighting and rendering. I also have some experience with digital sculpting and organic modeling.

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Bristol

Bachelor's Degree - BSc, Computer Science (2019 - 2022)

Grade: Second Class with Honours (2:1)

## "Unirea" National College

Romanian Baccalaureate Diploma: Maths - Computer Science (2015-2019)

Grade: 9.13 (Mathematics - 10, Physics - 9.6)

## **EXPERIENCE**

## University of Bristol

Teaching Assistant - Mathematics B (Jan 2021 - Jun 2021 & Jan 2022 – Jul 2022)

Helped a class of students getting through a series of lab sessions. Maintained weekly lab hours and problem-solving sessions.

#### Bristol Museum & Art Gallery

Frontend Developer (Nov 2020 - May 2021)

As a team of 4, I helped on creating a web application for the Bristol Museum & Art Gallery with the intention of showcasing what the museum has to offer and with the possibility of seeing the exhibits by searching through different art categories.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Jasmine Framework, AWS, Spring Boot

#### **PORTFOLIO**

Some projects from my portfolio (please see the full list by clicking on the portfolio)

## Shinbashi District (Link)

Recreated a beautiful shot of the Shinbashi District. The goal was to recreate the layout and the structures of the buildings and other objects as much as possible, while keeping an eye on the colours found in the photo.

Software used: Autodesk Maya, Substance 3D Painter, Unreal Engine, DaVinci Resolve

#### Motorcycle Concept (Link)

A rather futuristic motorcycle concept. Made in Maya with a few touches in Zbrush, textured in Substance, rendered in Arnold.

Software used: Autodesk Maya, Substance 3D Painter, ZBrush, Arnold